<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Developer Blog</title>
    <link>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Developer Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 00:39:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EmberJs</title>
      <link>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/emberjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 00:39:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/emberjs/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my new post which is about Ember.js. Are you getting started on ember.js? If yes then check out this post. In this post, I will explain what is ember.js, what are the features of ember.js, as there are so many JavaScript frameworks so why you use this, how to install it and how to start working with ember.js? I hope after reading this article you will somewhat understand ember.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Amazon S3</title>
      <link>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/amazons3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:39:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/amazons3/</guid>
      <description>As the number of users is increasing day by day on the internet, because of that database is becoming huge and complex. So, the need for storage is increasing every day and maintaining our database is a very tedious and time-consuming job. Sometimes our application fails because of not having enough space for data. It is very hard to predict that how much space we need in future for our applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Function Composition in JavaScript with Pipe</title>
      <link>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:39:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://prabhdeveloperblog.com/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>JavaScript is a very powerful language and it supports functional programming quite well. Function Composition tool makes JavaScript even more powerful. I hope in this article, I will provide you an easy example of function composition with the use of pipe in JavaScript. So, you can understand function composition in JavaScript and you can write short, clean and functional code.
What is Function Composition? Let&amp;rsquo;s start from basic by answering the question that what is function composition?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>